Hello friends, I am Junaid and you all are
heartily welcome to today's wonderful episode. Guys,
in today's video, we are basically going to
talk about 10 such important
questions which are asked the most.
If you want to become a relationship manager in ICICI Bank, then
in its interview, that is, for the
post of relationship manager in ICICI Bank,
if you want a job, then these 10 questions will
definitely be asked of you and if you feel
that you will be saved or something will happen, you will definitely
not be saved, these 10 questions will definitely be asked of you.
If you are a complete fresher and have
not worked anywhere till date, then these 10 questions are
very important for you, so guys,
you must listen to all these 10 questions. We will
start with question number one and this question
is basic, but many people make the
mistake here. The first question we have is "
Tell Me About Yourself." Okay,
tell us something about yourself. If you are having an interview
and you are asked this question, then you have to
tell only three things. Do
not drag it out for too long. First of all, tell about yourself.
Who are you? What's your name? Where do you
come from? And in the second one, you'll be
talking a little bit about your education. Okay, you'll be
telling a little bit about yourself.
You'll talk about these three things. Do
n't mention the fourth thing at all. Until then, the instructor
won't ask you any next question. You
can also modify this question a little bit according to your needs. Okay, if you
feel like, 'I have to
avoid this question,' or '
I have to avoid this thing,' then you can modify this question a little bit according to
your needs. That
means, you don't have to mention those things here
that you're afraid of getting into trouble for, or for which
you don't actually have an answer. So,
you have to tell about yourself properly, '
My name is Junaid, I come from there,
I want to work on this post.
In my education, I've done a B.Com, an
M.Com, a B.Sc., okay, and
my father does this.' That means, you
can talk a little bit about yourself in detail, but apart from these three points, the fourth
You don't have to get into the points at all.
Question number two: what does a relationship manager do?
This question is very
necessary. You're going to appear for an
interview to work as a relationship manager, and
you do
n't know about it, then this is a very bad thing.
First of all, you have to do thorough research about the post of a relationship manager.
We have made hundreds of videos on
what the work of a relationship manager is,
how much the salary is, and many other
things. I'll put links to some videos
in the description so you
can understand them properly. If
you still don't understand, then chat
on GPT and Google 3. Why do you want this job?
Okay, or
why are you choosing this bank? Why do you want a job in this bank? Or why do
you want a job in III
Bank? And why do you want a job in the
post of relationship manager?
These are two questions: first, why do you want a
job in this bank? Then,
why do you want a job in this post? So, let me
tell you a little about
its concept.  What he is actually
asking you is how much you know about ICICI Bank
and the answer to the same question is how much
you know about the post of Relationship Manager, how much
knowledge do you have, so brother, google about both the things
and how ICICI Bank actually
works, where it works, in what
ways it works, if the
examiner has asked you
why you want a job in this bank whose name is
ICICI Bank, then I will give you an
answer here, understand the sample, see
ICICI Bank is the second largest
bank in India, so here I will get to see many new
opportunities and I will get to
learn a lot, first of all
and at the same time I will try to help all the
clients who come to me to achieve their
financial goals, so that is
why I want to join ICICI Bank,
this is the answer to this, okay, if you think
that no sir, it is better than this  If this is the answer,
please write it in the comments. We
are also not great gurus, so please
tell us by writing in the comments. Guys, we have question number four.
Every day,
some changes or the other happen in the banking field.
Trends keep changing. So,
how will you keep yourself updated with the changing
banking rules and trends? So, you have to give a
simple answer that, Sir, I am a part of many such
programs and
publications where
financial news is
submitted on a daily or weekly basis. I keep
reading them and I keep reading them. So, the
examiner
can also ask questions from this like what happened last week
in financial terms and
conditions. So, you have to read it seriously. Only then will you be able to answer.
Now, you have
said in the air that I read
news, I read articles,
I have subscribed to publications, right?
Now, he will also ask you, brother,
what did you read? And you do
n't have any answer to this.  If yes, then you may get rejected from here,
so please, just talk nonsense, you have to
study a little bit as well.
We have question number five. The
HR has asked you to
tell me what qualities a perfect successful banker should have.
Tell me a little about it. Guys, you should
not speak too much on this, try to speak very less
but speak excellently. So,
you have to tell that there are some qualities which
make a banker perfect and successful.
Number one is good communication skills.
Your communication skills should be absolutely
excellent. Along with this,
you should also be able to write very well and
read very well. Your
verbal and return communication skills should be
very good. If you feel
that Janesh Sir, your communication skills,
Mashaallah Alhamdulillah, are very good.
How did you improve it? How did you
learn? We have written a book on this. You
can go and purchase that book. It is
in Hindi language.  The only second
quality you should have as a perfect banker is
maintaining and building strong relationships.
Yes, if someone meets you once, they should fall in
love with you.
This is how you will build your relationship. The
third quality you should have as a banker is
commitment. Well, the thing
I am talking about is that people do
n't have commitment. People
say they will get it done by Monday, but it does
n't happen by Tuesday. But it is
very important for you to live up to your commitment. Only then will
your relationship become
strong. You have to take special care of this thing.
And number four, we have
strong knowledge of finance. Yes, now look,
you are working in the banking field. The
finance sector is a strong sector
in itself. So, you have to
keep yourself up to date with all the rules, regulations, terms and conditions related to finance, only then can you
become a perfect banker. This is a long
answer, you can make it a little shorter.
And can you tell a little less guys now this
is question number seven suppose
our bank is working so much
percent sales we are getting so much percent
this then how will you improve our sales
as a relationship manager it is
obvious that a relationship manager does a lot of
sales so this question will obviously be
asked to you brother and if
this is not asked then something related to sales will definitely be
asked to you and you will definitely be
talked about improving sales
so please you should have a solid answer to this
okay can you tell how
can you do it look look the
most important thing to improve sales is
trust and trust is built when you
talk to someone, you will build your relationship
okay if you talk with love then the
relationship will be built and when your
relationship is built then you will ask for life a person gives his life for
money okay
so you will have to work hard on the relationship
first of all you can tell this to
four like this that I will build a relationship then
trust will be built  Then we
can bring sales from there, we can bring sales in a good brief. I
hope you are understanding all the things,
if you are, then please hit the
like button because this will be useful in the algorithm. Guys, the question that was
told earlier was
basically number six, now this is question
number seven, basically in this, Shan has asked
how many types of accounts are there
and you told that there are two types, there are
three types, so he
can take something from that, like
tell the difference between a savings account and a checking account, okay, so I have to
tell you, you have to read about it, first of all,
we can do transactions in a checking account, there is
no issue on a daily basis, and
we can do transactions in a savings account also,
but this is meant for saving, in this
we call it a savings account and in this
we are talking about saving money,
but in a checking account we
can do unlimited transactions and there are
many things, so you have to read and
go, okay.  So you must be answering it this way. Let
me tell you one more thing,
we have made another book of 200 questions,
okay, in which all the
questions related to any thing of private bank are
mentioned. If you have an interview and you are very
serious about your interview and are feeling
nervous about how to do it, what can I
ask, then please purchase that book of ours.
You will find the second link
in the description, its price is very low
and there are 200 questions which are
not generic, not general, first class
questions are kept in it, a lot of
research has been done on it, okay, earlier it
was free, now it has become paid, so you go and
purchase that book once. If you are
serious, your interview is, okay, let's
move on to question number eight,
how will you do cross selling with whichever client it is.
Okay, tell me a little about it.
See, the main thing we talk about is our
cross selling. There is a
guy to whom we have attached a product.  We
gave it to him and ended our relationship with him, but
this is wrong, okay, the bank does not like this, the
bank likes it, it is with a client to whom
we are offering 1010 products,
giving credit card, debit card, account, loan,
selling policies, doing everything,
that client is the best for us,
so the examiner is asking you
how will you do cross selling,
so you have to answer it in this way,
whichever product is aligned with whichever client,
okay, like if
a person opens a savings account, then we
can sell him a policy, it will sell easily,
or we can send him some terms,
so keeping this thing in mind, you have to
tell that sir, we should only
sell that product to that person with which it
is aligned, okay, like the charger
is aligned with the phone, okay, without the charger the phone
is incomplete, similarly we will give the product which
he needs, according to the need, whether he has
bought the phone or not, we are selling him something else, a
fan  If you are selling with a phone then
this won't work. He will say I do
n't need it, so we will try to give the same product
which is in alignment. In this
way we will be able to cross sell. Then by selling one with the other
we will create a chain through
which our products can be sold multiple times
and we can get more sales.
This is a basic answer to this. You
can make it a little more convincing and
better and you can also write to me in the comments.
I will shut you out. Guys,
question number nine is okay and this is the
most asked question and many banks
ask this. Today the question is
this, brother, look, in India and outside India,
banks are working very well everywhere, but
tell me what is the biggest challenge for the bank right now. Okay, tell me from where can the
threat come to the bank. So you have to answer this
regarding cyber security. Guys,
cyber security is such a topic which can be
dragged on for a very long time, but you should
not drag it on.
Banks are always at risk regarding cyber security due to someone's
transactions.  So that nothing goes wrong, no one's
belongings are stolen, no cyber attack happens,
a lot of things are happening every
day and for this we also have a proper cyber
security team, we are
repeatedly reporting things to them
that sir, this happened, that happened, so you
just have to tell them that sir, everything is fine, but the
cyber security people, I am
not a little sure that anything can happen there, so according to me, the
biggest threat to the bank
right now is cyber security, please
tell me in the comments, question number
10, HR has asked you that there is a
client who is closing his bank account
inside the bank, so how will you
handle him, see first of all,
when we open someone's account, we put a lot of pressure, so at the
time of closing, we have to
put a lot of pressure, sir, what
problem are you facing, why are you closing it,
ask 10 questions and if even after 10 questions the
answer is the same, I want to close it,
then cooperate with him completely,
close his account properly  You
should not behave rudely with him with respect, okay
so this is it and if you can give him any solution,
can feed him some good medicine, can
give him some sweet trophy, then definitely
try to give it, ask him to maintain his account,
if he
is a client of ICICI Bank, then guys, till now we have
told 10 questions which will be
asked during the interview for the post of Relationship Manager,
if you have any question in your mind,
any doubt, please ask in the comment, if it is
related to any bank, please
definitely ask, if you have come here for the first time, then
please subscribe to this channel right now
because it is absolutely
free and also if you want to talk to me,
want to connect with me, then
please me